cashrewards.com.au 2017-02-18

# Privacy Policy | Cashrewards

**Cashrewards™** is a trade mark used by Cashrewards Pty Limited ABN 72 150 888 136 (referred to in this policy as “Cashrewards”, “we” “us” or “our”). It is also our registered business name.

At Cashrewards™ the privacy of all our Members is of utmost importance. Cashrewards is committed to the safeguarding our Member’s **personal information**.

Cashrewards complies with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and is committed to collecting and holding Personal Information in accordance with the requirements of the APPs.

In this Privacy Policy we will explain to you the way that we manage Personal Information including: 

  1. What kinds of Personal Information does Cashrewards collect and hold?
  2. How does Cashrewards collect and hold Personal Information? 
  3. For what purposes does Cashrewards collect, hold, use and disclose Personal Information? 
  4. How can you access and correct information about you that we hold?
  5. How can you make a complaint about a breach of the AAPs or this privacy policy?
  6. What about your use of other websites?
  7. Other Information.

Defined terms used in this policy are:

 ** _introducer_** means those entities that recommend Cashrewards membership.

 ** _Cashrewards member_** means a person or entity that joins Cashrewards to take of advantage of the benefits of being part of Cashrewards membership.

 ** _personal information_** is information or an opinion (including information or an opinion forming part of a database), whether true or not, and whether recorded in a material form or not, about an identified individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable.

 ** _supplier_** means a supplier of goods or services to you or to us.

 **1\. What kinds of Personal Information does Cashrewards collect and hold?**

In order to provide you with the benefits of being a Member of Cashrewards including taking advantage of any special offers from our introducers or suppliers, we may collect, use and hold Personal Information about you. If we are not provided with all the Personal Information we request, we, our introducers and suppliers may not be able to provide to you with the full benefits of being a Cashrewards member and the products and services that are of most interest to you. 

The personal information we collect and hold is what is reasonably necessary for our business activities and functions. It may include:

  * your name, addresses, contact details, gender, occupation, company and if relevant, financial information, including credit card information, banking details, income information (however financial information including credit card numbers are stored internally only and are not held on by us on any external database);
  * customer reference numbers, Cashrewards membership number;
  * what products, services and offers from our introducers and suppliers that interest you;
  * what membership benefits interest you most and what benefits you have taken up;
  * any relationship you may have with other Cashrewards members (including other family members), our introducers and suppliers; and
  * your preferred shopping preferences and the types of promotions that may interest you.

We do not normally collect or store ‘sensitive information’, as defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (eg information about ethnic origin, religious beliefs or health). However, where we are required to and able to do so, we will ask for your consent before collecting your sensitive information and let you know the purpose at the same time.

 **2\. How does Cashrewards collect and hold my information?**

*  **Collection**

We generally collect and record your personal information directly from you. For example, we may collect the personal information you provide in your Account Settings and Rewards Profile, when you deal with us in any way including online, when you participate or take advantage of any benefits we, our introducers and suppliers offer, when you respond to any surveys, promotions or competitions held by us, our introducers and suppliers. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer hard drive, containing information about that user. A cookie can only be accessed across the Internet by the Web site that placed it there. Cookies are used by the Cashrewards to add functionality and security. 

You may choose to reject a cookie that the Cashrewards attempts to place on your computer, however you may then be limited in your use of some areas of our website.

*  **Other sources**

In addition to collecting person information directly from you or your dealing with us, we may also collect personal information from third parties such as our introducers and suppliers, and from analysing all the data we collect and hold. Where we will collect person information from a third party, at our request, we will only do so if it is unreasonable or impractical for us to collect it from you.

*  **Holding**

We take all reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information which we hold about you and to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorised alteration. Personal information is generally stored on our computer systems.

We take all reasonable steps to minimise the risk of loss, damage, unauthorised access and misuse of personal information we hold. We are not however responsible or liable for the security of data sent via the internet.

 **3\. For what purposes does Cashrewards collect, hold, use and disclose Personal Information?**

Cashrewards collects, holds and uses personal information primarily to fulfil our business functions and activities which include to:

  * meet our legal obligations;
  * identify our members, potential members and their representatives;
  * provide our benefits including cashback;
  * provide to you information and direct marketing about, and access to, benefits, promotions, goods and services offered by us, our introducers and suppliers which may be of interest to you;
  * process and track transactions between:
    * you and us; 
    * us and any of our introducers and suppliers; or 
    * you and any of our introducers or suppliers;
  * communicate with you;
  * seek your opinion or comments about our benefits or services or those of third parties;
  * personalise our communications with you including surveys; 
  * take steps to ensure that our information is accurate, up to date, complete and where appropriate relevant and that any offers you receive from us, our introducers or suppliers is personalised (in this respect we may disclose personal information to one or more third parties, who in turn may disclose to us personal information about you);
  * disclose demographic and profile information with our introducers and suppliers (for example, we might disclose that 2895 of our members live in a particular town or suburb, or that 37% of our members have indicated an interest in sport); and
  * manage any complaints or enquires you may have.

We usually disclose the personal information we collect to our related entities, service providers and contractors in connection with the provision of our services and the benefits we provide to you. 

We also disclose personal information to third parties to assist us

In addition, we may collect, use, hold and disclose personal information for another purpose but only if it would be reasonable to expect that the other purpose is related to any of the primary purposes identified above; and where the use or disclosure is permitted, required or authorised by law.

With respect to any direct marketing from us, you may opt out of receiving it. The direct marketing material will advise you how to opt out if you wish to do so.

We are not likely to disclose personal information to overseas recipients. 

We may de-identify personal information. When we do so, the information may be disclosed on an anonymous basis and may be used for any useful general analytical purpose. 

**4\. How can you enquire about, access and correct the personal information we hold about you?**

*  **Access**

You may request access to your Personal Information unless:

  * the access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of other individuals;
  * the request for access is frivolous or vexatious;
  * there are existing or anticipated legal proceedings between Boost Mobile and you and the information would not be accessible by the process of discovery in those proceedings;
  * giving access would be unlawful; or
  * such access can be denied under the APPs, any law or by a law enforcement agency.

If you wish to access your personal information or have an enquiry about privacy, please contact our Privacy Officer at: privacy@cashrewards.com.au or alternatively, you can write to us at: 

Privacy Officer Suite 4306   
4 Daydream Street   
Warriewood NSW 2102 

Before we provide you with access to your personal information we may require some proof of identity. We may charge a reasonable fee for giving access to your personal information if your request requires substantial effort on our part. 

* **Correction:**

We always try to make sure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If at any time you believe the personal information that we hold about you is incomplete or inaccurate, please let us know. We will use all reasonable efforts to correct the information. If you need to correct your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer at one of the above contact points.

 **5\. How can you make a compliant about a breach of the APPs or this Privacy Policy?**

We are committed to constantly improving our procedures so that your personal information is treated appropriately. If you feel that we have failed to deal with your personal information in accordance with the APPs or this policy, please contact our Privacy Officer at: privacy@cashrewards.com.au or alternatively, you can write to us at: 

Privacy Officer   
Suite 4306   
4 Daydream Street   
Warriewood NSW 2102 

Our Privacy Officer will listen to your concerns and grievances; discuss with you the ways in which we can remedy the situation; and put in place an action plan to resolve your complaint and improve our information handling procedures if appropriate.

Our Privacy Officer may request that you put your complaint in writing and will promptly inform you in writing of the results of his investigations into your complaint including what steps will be taken, if any, to address your concerns. If you are not satisfied with the outcome of the resolution of your complaint by us, you may refer the complaint to the Privacy Commissioner for further investigation.

 **6\. What about your use of other websites?**

Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the owners or operators of those other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website to read the privacy policies of the other websites you use. 

**7\. Other Information**

Cashrewards reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and we encourage you to review this policy from time to time. This privacy policy is current as of [insert date]. Any changes to this privacy policy will be displayed by us on our website [insert period] before the changes take effect.

This privacy policy must be read in conjunction with any other terms and conditions that may govern our relationship include the terms and conditions set out at [insert link]. If you are an employee of Cashrewards this privacy policy does not apply to you in your capacity as an employee.

Further information about privacy and the relevant law may be obtained from the Privacy Commissioner at www.oaic.gov.au or [emailenquiries@oaic.gov.au](mailto:emailenquiries@oaic.gov.au).
